pnop.com 2013-01-16

# Privacy Policy - PNOP.com

### Your privacy is our top concern.

We work hard to earn and keep your trust, so we adhere to the following principles to protect your privacy: 

  1. We do not rent or sell your personally identifiable information to third parties for marketing purposes.
  2. We do not share your contact information with another User without your consent.
  3. Any personally identifiable information that you provide will be secured with industry standard protocols and technology.

We provide this Privacy Policy to inform you of our policies and procedures regarding the collection, use and disclosure of the personal data and other information we receive from Users of the Site. 

We may update this Privacy Policy from time to time and will handle your information in accordance with the version that was in place when you provided it. We will notify you of any changes by posting the new Privacy Policy on the Site. We reserve the right to modify this Privacy Policy at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to this Privacy Policy, we will notify you here, by email, or by means of a notice on the home page of the Site. Unless otherwise defined in this Privacy Policy, terms used in this Privacy Policy have the same meanings as in our Terms of Use. By continuing to use the Site after notice of changes have been sent to you or published on the Site, you are consenting to the changes. 

The Site is a website created by and dedicated to fans of movies and TV series. With our unique approach to your needs and expectations the Site helps you to find anything you want to know about your favorite movies or celebrities. We provide you with the most comprehensive database about actors, TV series and movies. Moreover, the Site offers you a search engine and much, much more. We provide you with photo gallery, previews, reviews, interviews, movie trailers, TV clips and gossips about your favorite actors and actresses. We will recommend you movies you will like based on your mood-kind and we notify you best events on our Site. You may award and rate your favorite movies or actors. You may configure and personalize the Site according to your unique preferences. You can also connect your Facebook, Twitter or Google+ account to the Site. Based on recommendations of the Users of the Site we still develop, improve and extend services of our Site to ensure that you will find here anything you are looking for. If our Site does not satisfy you or you think that it should have something you find interesting or helpful, we would really appreciate it, if you could share your opinion with us and tell what could be changed or improve about the Site. 

You willingly provide us certain personal information, which we collect in order to allow you to benefit fully from the Site. If you have any hesitation about providing such information to us or otherwise used in any manner provided for in this Privacy Policy and the Terms of Use, you should not become the User of the Site. 

#### The Site and third parties’ sites

This Privacy Policy applies solely to the Site. The Site may contain links to third parties’ sites that are not owned or controlled by the Owner. The Owner has no control over, and assumes no responsibility for, the content, privacy policies, or practices of any third party’s site. You agree that you are responsible for reviewing and understanding the privacy policies (if any) of any third parties’ sites you may access through this Site. By using this Site, you release the Owner from any and all liability arising from your use of any third party’s site to which this Site may be linked. Our primary goals in collecting information are to provide and improve the Site and the related features, to administer your subscription and participation in the affiliate program and to enable Users to enjoy and easily navigate the Site. Below are the types and categories of information that we collect. 

#### Personal information collected

We collect your personal information in the following ways: 

#### Account

In order to become a User, you do not need to create an account on our Site. However, in order to access some features (e.g. participation in the affiliate program) of the services or other elements of the Site, you will have to create your account. When creating your account you benefit from number of different services we provide to help you take advantage of our unique approach to your needs and expectations about movies. In this respect you are required to provide the following contact information, which you recognize and expressly acknowledge is personal information allowing others, including the Owner, to identify you: email address, username and password chosen by you. It is important that you must keep your account password secure and confidential. 

#### Log data

When you visit the Site or use the Site, whether as a Site subscriber or a non-registered User just browsing our servers the Owner automatically records information about your use of the Site and your visit to the Site ("Log Data"). The Log Data may include information such as your computer's Internet Protocol (IP) address, your browser type, what software you were using, the web page you were visiting immediately prior to visiting our Site, pages of our Site that you visited, the time spent on those pages, information you searched for on our Site, access times and dates, and other statistics. We use this information to monitor and analyze use of the Site and for the Site's technical administration, to improve our Site's functionality and User-friendliness, and to better tailor it to our Users' needs. We also use this information to verify that Users of the Site meet the criteria required to process their requests. 

#### Cookies

Like most sites, we use cookies and web log files to track the use of the Site. A cookie is a tiny data file which resides on your computer and allows the Owner to recognize you as a User when you return to the Site using the same computer and web browser. If your browser settings do not allow cookies, you may not be able to use the Site. Like the information you enter at registration, cookie and log file data are used to customize your experience on the Site.   
One type of cookie, known as a "persistent" cookie, is set once you’ve logged in to your account. The next time you visit the Site, the persistent cookie will allow us to recognize you as a registered User, so you will not need to log in before using the Site.   
Additionally, if you log out of your account you will need to re-enter your password the next time in order to log in to your account. Another type of cookie, called a "session" cookie, is used to identify a particular visit to the Site. Session cookies expire after a short time or when you close your web browser.   
Moreover, the Site may use local shared objects, commonly called a "flash cookies" for purposes such as storing Users’ preferences. You may manage or opt out of your flash cookies [here](http://www.macromedia.com/support/documentation/en/flashplayer/help/settings_manager06.html).   
In the course of serving advertisements or optimizing services to our Users, we may allow authorized third parties to place or recognize a unique cookie on your browser. Any information provided to third parties through such cookies will not be personally identifiable. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by third parties, please click [here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp). Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies, but you can reset your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. Unfortunately, if your browser settings do not allow cookies or you opt to refuse all cookies, you may not be able to use the Site. The Owner does not store personal data in the cookies. 

#### Web beacons

We allow other companies, called ad networks, to serve advertisements to Users. Ad networks include third party ad servers, ad agencies, ad technology vendors and research firms. 

To deliver these ads properly, the Site may include a file, called a web beacon, from these ad networks within pages served by the Site so the networks may provide anonymized, aggregated auditing, research and reporting for advertisers as well as to target ads to you while you visit other sites. 

Because your web browser must request these advertisements and web beacons from the ad network’s servers, these companies can view, edit or set their own cookies, just as if you had requested a web page from their site. 

These general targets may also be used by ad networks to display targeted ads on other sites as a substitute for random, irrelevant ads. The Owner does not provide personally identifiable information to any advertiser or any other third party. 

#### Log files, IP addresses and information about your computer

Due to the communications standards on the Internet, when you visit the Site we automatically receive the URL of the site from which you came and the site to which you are going when you leave the Site. We also receive the Internet protocol (IP) address of your computer (or the proxy server you use to access the World Wide Web), your computer operating system and type of web browser you are using, email patterns, as well as the name of your ISP. This information is used to analyze overall trends to help us improve the Site. The linkage between your IP address and your personally identifiable information is not shared with third-parties without your permission or except when required by law. 

#### Communications

The Owner will communicate with you through email and notices posted on the Site or through other means available through the Site, including text and other forms of messaging. The Owner may use your email address without further consent for non-marketing or administrative purposes (such as notifying you of material Site changes or for Users service purposes). If we send any communications to you via the carrier service with which you have a mobile communications subscription or otherwise have access, you understand you will pay any service fees associated with any such access (including text messaging charges for messages to your mobile device). Please be aware that you will always receive certain emails from the Owner related to the proper functioning of your account. You can change your email and contact preferences at any time by logging into your account and amending your email notification choices. 

#### Sharing information with third parties

The Owner takes the privacy of Users very seriously. We do not sell, rent, or otherwise provide your personally identifiable information to third parties for marketing purposes. We will only share your personally identifiable information with third parties to carry out your instructions or to provide specific services or information. These third parties do not retain, share, or store any personally identifiable information except to provide these services and they are bound by confidentiality agreements which limit their use of such information.   
We may provide aggregated anonymous data about the usage of our Site to third parties for such purposes as we deem, in our sole discretion, to be appropriate, including to prospective advertisers on the Site. 

#### Teaming with third parties to offer combined services

The Owner may offer the Site in connection with other sites (including updates about the Site) or may team with other online services to give you the combined results of both services or additional services and benefits. Platform Applications can be designed by Platform Developers or by a subset of Platform Developers with whom the Owner has more closely aligned (“Partners”). 

In the case of Partners, we do some vetting and we only work with trusted Partners. Because of Owner’s trust in these Partners, platform applications or services designed by a Partner may be automatically granted permission to access account information to provide the combined services. 

For platform applications designed by most Platform Developers, you will be asked to confirm acceptance of the Platform Developers’ respective privacy policies and User agreements, which have not necessarily been reviewed or approved by the Owner. In these cases, it will be your choice whether or not to make use of the services and whether to proceed under the Platform Developers’ terms. 

Platform Developers are required to agree to restrictions on access, storage and usage of your information. However, while we typically enter into contractual agreements and take technical steps to restrict possible misuse of such information by such Platform Developers, we may not screen or approve Platform Developers, and we cannot and do not guarantee that all Platform Developers will abide by such restrictions and agreements. 

The Owner is not responsible for your use of or inability to use any platform applications, including the content, accuracy, or reliability of such applications and the privacy practices or other policies of Platform Developers. 

The Owner allows other companies to place advertisements on the Site. These companies use technology to deliver advertisements you see on the Site directly to your browser. In doing so, they may automatically receive your IP address. Other companies that place advertising on the Site may have the ability to use cookies and/or web beacons to collect information, including information about your usage of the Site. We do not control the processes that advertisers use to collect information. However, IP addresses, cookies and web beacons alone generally cannot be used to identify individuals, only machines. Therefore, advertisers and others whose advertisements or content may appear on the Site generally will not know who you are unless you provide additional information to them, by responding to an advertisement, by entering into an agreement with them, or by some other means. 

#### Legal disclaimer

The Owner cooperates with government and law enforcement officials and private parties to enforce and comply with the law. We will disclose any information about you to government or law enforcement officials or private parties as we, in our sole discretion, believe necessary or appropriate to respond to claims and legal process (including without limitation subpoenas), to protect the property and rights of the Owner or a third party, to protect the safety of the public or any person, or to prevent or stop activity we consider to be illegal or unethical. 

#### Disclosures to others

We may also disclose your personal and other information you provide, to another third party as part of reorganization or a sale of the assets of the Owner division or company. Any third party to which we transfer or sell Owner’s assets will have the right to continue to use the personal and other information that you provide to us. 

#### Phishing

Identity theft and the practice currently known as "phishing" are of great concern to the Owner. Safeguarding information to help protect you from identity theft is a top priority. We do not and will not, at any time, request your credit card information, your account ID, login password in a non-secure or unsolicited email or telephone communication. 

#### Aggregate information and non-identifying information

We may share aggregated information that does not include personal Information and we may otherwise disclose non-identifying information and Log Data with third parties for industry analysis, demographic profiling and other purposes. Any aggregated information shared in these contexts will not contain your personal information. 

#### International transfer

Your information may be transferred to and maintained on computers located outside of your state, province, country or other governmental jurisdiction where the privacy laws may not be as protective as those in your jurisdiction. Your consent to this Privacy Policy followed by your submission of such information represents your agreement to such transfer. 

#### Links to other sites

Our Site contains links to other web sites. If you choose to visit an advertiser by clicking on a banner ad or other type of advertisement, or click on another third party’s link, you will be directed to that third party's web site. The fact that we link to a web site or present a banner ad or other type of advertisement is not an endorsement, authorization or representation of our affiliation with that third party, nor is it an endorsement of their privacy or information security policies or practices. We do not exercise control over third parties’ web sites. These other web sites may place their own cookies or other files on your computer, collect data or solicit personal information from you. Other sites follow different rules regarding the use or disclosure of the personal information you submit to them. We encourage you to read the privacy policies or statements of the other web sites you visit. 

#### Accessing and changing your account information

You can review the information you provided us and make any desired changes to them, or to the settings for your account including your email at any time by logging in to your account on the Site. Please be aware that even after your request for a change is processed, the Owner may, for a time, retain residual information about you in its backup and/or archival copies of its database. We take your rights seriously and encourage you to use them if you deem this to be appropriate. You may exercise these rights by emailing us at [support@pnop.com](mailto:support@pnop.com). 

#### Deactivating your account

You can also deactivate your account through the Site, in which case you can still use the Site, but the Owner may not be able to provide certain services to you. If you deactivate your account, we may retain certain data contributed by you if we believe it may be necessary to prevent fraud or future abuse, or for legitimate business purposes, such as analysis of aggregated, non-personally identifiable data, account recovery, or if required by law. In order to deactivate your account please visit "Deactivate Account" section associated with your account or you may submit a relevant declaration and send it to the following email address: [support@pnop.com](mailto:support@pnop.com). 

#### Your obligations

As a User, you have certain obligations imposed by applicable law and regulations: 

  1. You must, at all times, respect the terms and conditions of the then-current Privacy Policy and the Terms of Use. This includes respecting all intellectual property rights which may belong to third parties.
  2. You must not download or otherwise disseminate any information which may be deemed to be injurious, violent, offensive, racist or xenophobic.

Any violation of these guidelines may lead to the restriction, suspension or termination of your account by the Owner, as we take these principles seriously and consider them to be the basis on which our Users adhere to the Site and the services which it offers. 

#### Security

We will make any legally required disclosures of any breach of the security, confidentiality, or integrity of your unencrypted electronically stored "personal data" (as defined in applicable laws related to security breach notification) to you via email or conspicuous posting on this Site in the most expedient time possible and without unreasonable delay, insofar as consistent with: (i) the legitimate needs of law enforcement; or (ii) any measures necessary to determine the scope of the breach and restore the reasonable integrity of the data system. 

#### Data retention policy

The Owner may retain your account information indefinitely, regardless of whether you have disabled your account on the Site. The Owner will retain Log Data consistent with applicable legal requirements. Generally, at a minimum, the Owner will retain the Log Data collected from you in its active, internal company databases for six months, at which point it will migrate such Log Data to its offline archival systems, where the Owner will retain the Log Data for a period of three years (together, the "Retention Period"). After the Retention Period, the Owner will purge the Log Data from its systems. In the event of an investigation by law enforcement or a response to claims or legal process, we may retain the Log Data until such investigation or process is completed, which may be longer than the Retention Period. 

#### Statement

The data controller of your personal data is Red Sky Sp. z o.o., a company incorporated under the laws of Poland, with its registered office in Szczecin, at Aleja Piastów 22, Szczecin 71-064, Poland, registered in the Entrepreneurs Register conducted by the National Court Register maintained by the District Court in Szczecin, XIII Commercial Department, under KRS number 0000209107, NIP (tax identification number): 642-26-83-651, REGON number: 276822679, amount of the share capital of PLN 1.046.000,00 covered in whole.   
Red Sky Sp. z o. o. hereby declares as follows: 

  1. All data provided in the Register Form or/and Contact Form will be processed in order to allow the use of the Site. All data provided to the Owner will be stored and processed by the Owner in accordance with the provisions of the Polish Act of 18 July 2002 on providing services by electronic means (Journal of Laws of 2002 No 144, item 1204 as amended), as well as in accordance with the Polish Act of 29 August 1997 on the protection of personal data (consolidated text: Journal of Laws of 2002 No 101, item 926 as amended). 
  2. All personal data transferred to Red Sky will be stored by Red Sky in Red Sky’s database. 
  3. Red Sky shall ensure the safety of Users’ personal data and it has implemented appropriate technical and organizational security measures as set forth in the Polish Act of 29 August 1997 on the protection of personal data and has met the requirements specified in the provisions referred to thereof, in particular to protect the personal data to be processed against accidental or unlawful destruction or accidental loss, alteration, unauthorized disclosure or access, in particular where the processing involves the transmission of data over a network, and against all other unlawful forms of processing. These measures ensure a level of security appropriate to the risks presented by the processing and the nature of the data to be protected having regard to the state of the art. 
  4. You have the right to verify, review and correct your personal data processed by Red Sky, which also requires you notify the Red Sky any changes thereof. The right can be exercised by you independently introducing changes in the Register Form of your account or by sending a relevant request to the following address [support@pnop.com](mailto:support@pnop.com). 
  5. You have the right to withdraw your consent to the processing of your personal data, giving the Red Sky a notice to that effect. Though you provide your personal data to Red Sky voluntarily, refusal to provide them may render entry into the agreement with Red Sky and access to the Site or services impossible. 
  6. Red Sky fulfills all the requirements provided for in the Polish Act of 29 August on the protection of personal data. 
  7. Red Sky shall have the right to disclose the personal data only to the authorities entitled under the provisions of the law in force (e.g. a court, the police), in cases specified in the Terms of Use and resulting from the law in force. 
  8. After reviewing the above Privacy Policy, by using the Site, and especially by clicking "Sign up" or "Sign in" during the registration process, you hereby: 
    1. Consent to the processing and use by the Red Sky all the personal data provided to Red Sky, including data obtained as a result of your use of the Site, for the following purposes: (i) User's use of and registration on the Site (a possibility of using the functionalities offered by the Site; a User is a party to the agreement on services provided by electronic means); (ii) processing complaints; (iii) replying to correspondence sent through the Contact Form; (iv) technical operation of the Site; and (v) maintaining the Site’s statistics.
    2. Consent to transfer of your personal data abroad and in particular to Red Sky’s affiliated companies or associated entities, or to Red Sky’s parent company, with their registered office outside the Poland, for the purposes of processing in computer systems belonging to the Red Sky and its business partners. You understand that the above entities may be located in countries that do not guarantee the same level of personal data protection as the level guaranteed in Poland.
    3. Agree that your consent remains valid for the entire period of your use of the Site.
    4. Declare and confirm that you have read Terms of Use, you understand them and you will comply with them, both in its current wording and with any later amendments.

#### How to contact us

If you have questions or comments about this Privacy Policy or you want to report abuse or neglect of this Privacy Policy, please email us at [support@pnop.com](mailto:support@pnop.com).
